Erdem Celik

I finished my education in Istanbul. I have gained experience in multiple business activities. Developing in new and growing areas has always increased me a lot. I prefer to be together with my friends in my spare time. I am also continuing on the e-commerce project.





Bahçelievler, İstanbul, Türkiye

@Clikerdem

+905532760477

26 May, 1988

WORK EXPERIENCES

Barmaid

Ritz-Carlton Istanbul

05/2004 - 10/2006

Istanbul

Sales representatives

Atu Duty Free

04/2008 - 10/2018 Istanbul

Facility Management Officer

Sea Pearl Istanbul

10/2019 - Present Istanbul

WEB SITE

https://erdemcelik.netlify.app/ ♂

EDUCATION

Business

Istanbul University

09/2021 - Present

İstanbul

Science

Bahçelievler Cumhuriyet High school

09/1999 - 05/2002

İstanbul

Law Vocational School

Istanbul University

İstanbul

SKILLS

REFERENCES

Yalçın Tanrınıan (0530) 159 12 56

Kuzu Group General Manager

Ümit Acar (0536) 647 61 56

Atü Duty Free Sale Manager

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Deutch

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Web Development

Travel

Bicycle

Philosophy

History

09/2018 - 05/2020

CERTIFICATES

Active Advanced English Course

Holiday Inn Opera PMS

IHG Hospitality

Microsoft Office Pluralsight

Driver Licence B Class

MY DAILY ACTIVITY

